{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788219150","data":{"timestamp":" 946788219149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 3e5ef0bf-eb38-4856-a9e6-dd31f2526c1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788242037","data":{"timestamp":" 946788242037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_alihepa_ghafula_kunukia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788248707","data":{"timestamp":" 946788248707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akitaka_amewaua_mekundu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788255355","data":{"timestamp":" 946788255355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788262833","data":{"timestamp":" 946788262833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788269484","data":{"timestamp":" 946788269483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amshike_mwangza_aliitoa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788276938","data":{"timestamp":" 946788276937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amshike_mwangza_aliitoa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788283579","data":{"timestamp":" 946788283579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuepuka_urafiki_tulijua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788290227","data":{"timestamp":" 946788290227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_utavuna_kupanga_aliumwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788296835","data":{"timestamp":" 946788296835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikujua_mvulana_akaosha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788303496","data":{"timestamp":" 946788303496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuzirai_waliuza_kuchuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788310123","data":{"timestamp":" 946788310123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788317553","data":{"timestamp":" 946788317553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788328171","data":{"timestamp":" 946788328171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788336732","data":{"timestamp":" 946788336731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788342348","data":{"timestamp":" 946788342348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788352939","data":{"timestamp":" 946788352939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788360172","data":{"timestamp":" 946788360172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788367749","data":{"timestamp":" 946788367749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788373659","data":{"timestamp":" 946788373658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788380414","data":{"timestamp":" 946788380414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" eacc256a-8518-45ea-9ffc-09b983167fd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788398049","data":{"timestamp":" 946788398049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788405171","data":{"timestamp":" 946788405171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788414999","data":{"timestamp":" 946788414999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788422180","data":{"timestamp":" 946788422180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788429995","data":{"timestamp":" 946788429995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788437243","data":{"timestamp":" 946788437243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788445693","data":{"timestamp":" 946788445693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788452815","data":{"timestamp":" 946788452814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788459495","data":{"timestamp":" 946788459494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788466867","data":{"timestamp":" 946788466867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788476198","data":{"timestamp":" 946788476198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788477876","data":{"timestamp":" 946788477876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788482355","data":{"timestamp":" 946788482355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788483795","data":{"timestamp":" 946788483795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788490024","data":{"timestamp":" 946788490024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788499342","data":{"timestamp":" 946788499342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" b8b83ce5-7eef-4f0b-b426-fc0d1ac1632f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788511872","data":{"timestamp":" 946788511872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788512464","data":{"timestamp":" 946788512464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788513195","data":{"timestamp":" 946788513195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788513374","data":{"timestamp":" 946788513374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788514163","data":{"timestamp":" 946788514162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788515198","data":{"timestamp":" 946788515197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788517956","data":{"timestamp":" 946788517956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788520350","data":{"timestamp":" 946788520350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788523051","data":{"timestamp":" 946788523051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788524813","data":{"timestamp":" 946788524813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788527019","data":{"timestamp":" 946788527019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788530110","data":{"timestamp":" 946788530110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788532262","data":{"timestamp":" 946788532262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TULIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788532945","data":{"timestamp":" 946788532945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" FOLENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788534198","data":{"timestamp":" 946788534198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788535876","data":{"timestamp":" 946788535875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788536618","data":{"timestamp":" 946788536617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" KUCHOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788537471","data":{"timestamp":" 946788537471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788538357","data":{"timestamp":" 946788538357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788539097","data":{"timestamp":" 946788539096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788539759","data":{"timestamp":" 946788539759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788542859","data":{"timestamp":" 946788542859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788545766","data":{"timestamp":" 946788545766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788547808","data":{"timestamp":" 946788547807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788549993","data":{"timestamp":" 946788549993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788552800","data":{"timestamp":" 946788552800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788555700","data":{"timestamp":" 946788555699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788557682","data":{"timestamp":" 946788557682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788559498","data":{"timestamp":" 946788559497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788561415","data":{"timestamp":" 946788561415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788564233","data":{"timestamp":" 946788564233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TULISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788564776","data":{"timestamp":" 946788564775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788564921","data":{"timestamp":" 946788564921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788565320","data":{"timestamp":" 946788565319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788566156","data":{"timestamp":" 946788566156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788567094","data":{"timestamp":" 946788567093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" KUPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788567802","data":{"timestamp":" 946788567802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788567962","data":{"timestamp":" 946788567962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788568728","data":{"timestamp":" 946788568728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788571743","data":{"timestamp":" 946788571743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788573534","data":{"timestamp":" 946788573534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788576165","data":{"timestamp":" 946788576165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788579133","data":{"timestamp":" 946788579133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788581433","data":{"timestamp":" 946788581433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788583913","data":{"timestamp":" 946788583913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788586019","data":{"timestamp":" 946788586019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788588771","data":{"timestamp":" 946788588770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788591237","data":{"timestamp":" 946788591237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788593796","data":{"timestamp":" 946788593795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TULIFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788594279","data":{"timestamp":" 946788594278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788594803","data":{"timestamp":" 946788594802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788595599","data":{"timestamp":" 946788595598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788596263","data":{"timestamp":" 946788596262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788596914","data":{"timestamp":" 946788596914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788597002","data":{"timestamp":" 946788597001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788597612","data":{"timestamp":" 946788597611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" WIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788600958","data":{"timestamp":" 946788600958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788604265","data":{"timestamp":" 946788604265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788606774","data":{"timestamp":" 946788606774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788609769","data":{"timestamp":" 946788609769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788611588","data":{"timestamp":" 946788611588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788613650","data":{"timestamp":" 946788613650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788617026","data":{"timestamp":" 946788617025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788619228","data":{"timestamp":" 946788619228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788621791","data":{"timestamp":" 946788621791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788621927","data":{"timestamp":" 946788621927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788622875","data":{"timestamp":" 946788622875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788623950","data":{"timestamp":" 946788623949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788624624","data":{"timestamp":" 946788624623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788625079","data":{"timestamp":" 946788625079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788625718","data":{"timestamp":" 946788625717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788626265","data":{"timestamp":" 946788626265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788626753","data":{"timestamp":" 946788626752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788628141","data":{"timestamp":" 946788628141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788628807","data":{"timestamp":" 946788628805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" KULIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788629406","data":{"timestamp":" 946788629405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788633462","data":{"timestamp":" 946788633462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788636067","data":{"timestamp":" 946788636067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788638702","data":{"timestamp":" 946788638702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788641841","data":{"timestamp":" 946788641841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788643673","data":{"timestamp":" 946788643673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788645257","data":{"timestamp":" 946788645256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788647232","data":{"timestamp":" 946788647232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788649621","data":{"timestamp":" 946788649621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788651616","data":{"timestamp":" 946788651616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788653947","data":{"timestamp":" 946788653947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788657091","data":{"timestamp":" 946788657091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788658939","data":{"timestamp":" 946788658939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788661416","data":{"timestamp":" 946788661414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788661796","data":{"timestamp":" 946788661796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788662802","data":{"timestamp":" 946788662802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788663314","data":{"timestamp":" 946788663314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788664273","data":{"timestamp":" 946788664273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788664928","data":{"timestamp":" 946788664927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788665553","data":{"timestamp":" 946788665553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" YAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788668727","data":{"timestamp":" 946788668727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788670876","data":{"timestamp":" 946788670876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788673201","data":{"timestamp":" 946788673201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788675045","data":{"timestamp":" 946788675045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788677365","data":{"timestamp":" 946788677365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788680500","data":{"timestamp":" 946788680500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788682209","data":{"timestamp":" 946788682209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788684661","data":{"timestamp":" 946788684661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788685416","data":{"timestamp":" 946788685416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788686242","data":{"timestamp":" 946788686241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" WALIRANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788686748","data":{"timestamp":" 946788686747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" RANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788687700","data":{"timestamp":" 946788687700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788688343","data":{"timestamp":" 946788688343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788688962","data":{"timestamp":" 946788688961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788689895","data":{"timestamp":" 946788689894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788690343","data":{"timestamp":" 946788690343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788690820","data":{"timestamp":" 946788690820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788691783","data":{"timestamp":" 946788691783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" MASHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788694675","data":{"timestamp":" 946788694674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788697715","data":{"timestamp":" 946788697715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788699819","data":{"timestamp":" 946788699819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788702570","data":{"timestamp":" 946788702570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788705582","data":{"timestamp":" 946788705582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788707058","data":{"timestamp":" 946788707058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788710473","data":{"timestamp":" 946788710473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788716352","data":{"timestamp":" 946788716351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788718239","data":{"timestamp":" 946788718239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788720953","data":{"timestamp":" 946788720953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788724161","data":{"timestamp":" 946788724160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788726572","data":{"timestamp":" 946788726572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788727884","data":{"timestamp":" 946788727883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIPOVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788729636","data":{"timestamp":" 946788729635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788730446","data":{"timestamp":" 946788730446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788731300","data":{"timestamp":" 946788731300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" CHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788731781","data":{"timestamp":" 946788731780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788733033","data":{"timestamp":" 946788733032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" KUZIANGIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788734073","data":{"timestamp":" 946788734073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" MITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788734533","data":{"timestamp":" 946788734533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788735163","data":{"timestamp":" 946788735163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" UANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788738295","data":{"timestamp":" 946788738295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788740992","data":{"timestamp":" 946788740992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788745566","data":{"timestamp":" 946788745566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788748032","data":{"timestamp":" 946788748031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788750016","data":{"timestamp":" 946788750016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788752705","data":{"timestamp":" 946788752705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788755534","data":{"timestamp":" 946788755534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788757812","data":{"timestamp":" 946788757812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788759531","data":{"timestamp":" 946788759531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788761226","data":{"timestamp":" 946788761226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788763942","data":{"timestamp":" 946788763942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788764535","data":{"timestamp":" 946788764534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788765469","data":{"timestamp":" 946788765469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788765659","data":{"timestamp":" 946788765658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788766403","data":{"timestamp":" 946788766403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" VIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788766657","data":{"timestamp":" 946788766656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788767292","data":{"timestamp":" 946788767291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788768691","data":{"timestamp":" 946788768691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788769040","data":{"timestamp":" 946788769039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788769528","data":{"timestamp":" 946788769528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788773231","data":{"timestamp":" 946788773230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788775434","data":{"timestamp":" 946788775434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788777796","data":{"timestamp":" 946788777796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788779781","data":{"timestamp":" 946788779781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788782801","data":{"timestamp":" 946788782800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788786518","data":{"timestamp":" 946788786518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788788775","data":{"timestamp":" 946788788775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788791397","data":{"timestamp":" 946788791397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788793183","data":{"timestamp":" 946788793183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788794909","data":{"timestamp":" 946788794909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788797327","data":{"timestamp":" 946788797327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788797781","data":{"timestamp":" 946788797780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788798432","data":{"timestamp":" 946788798432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788799726","data":{"timestamp":" 946788799726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788799939","data":{"timestamp":" 946788799938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788800542","data":{"timestamp":" 946788800541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788801798","data":{"timestamp":" 946788801785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788802497","data":{"timestamp":" 946788802497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788803360","data":{"timestamp":" 946788803360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" MITUNGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788803797","data":{"timestamp":" 946788803797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788804934","data":{"timestamp":" 946788804934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788805649","data":{"timestamp":" 946788805649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788808281","data":{"timestamp":" 946788808281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788810689","data":{"timestamp":" 946788810689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788811854","data":{"timestamp":" 946788811853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788813750","data":{"timestamp":" 946788813750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788816172","data":{"timestamp":" 946788816172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788821209","data":{"timestamp":" 946788821209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788823854","data":{"timestamp":" 946788823854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788825477","data":{"timestamp":" 946788825477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788828491","data":{"timestamp":" 946788828491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788830741","data":{"timestamp":" 946788830741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788833067","data":{"timestamp":" 946788833067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788834988","data":{"timestamp":" 946788834988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788837532","data":{"timestamp":" 946788837532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788838795","data":{"timestamp":" 946788838794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" ALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788839570","data":{"timestamp":" 946788839569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788840194","data":{"timestamp":" 946788840194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788840967","data":{"timestamp":" 946788840966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788841519","data":{"timestamp":" 946788841519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788842824","data":{"timestamp":" 946788842824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" AKIWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788843352","data":{"timestamp":" 946788843352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788844606","data":{"timestamp":" 946788844605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" KUHUDHURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788845458","data":{"timestamp":" 946788845458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788845685","data":{"timestamp":" 946788845684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788846516","data":{"timestamp":" 946788846516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" KUJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788851236","data":{"timestamp":" 946788851236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788853559","data":{"timestamp":" 946788853559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788855382","data":{"timestamp":" 946788855382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788857377","data":{"timestamp":" 946788857377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788859571","data":{"timestamp":" 946788859570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788861555","data":{"timestamp":" 946788861555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788863563","data":{"timestamp":" 946788863563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788867037","data":{"timestamp":" 946788867037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788869735","data":{"timestamp":" 946788869735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788871504","data":{"timestamp":" 946788871504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788873727","data":{"timestamp":" 946788873727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788875648","data":{"timestamp":" 946788875648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788877901","data":{"timestamp":" 946788877900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788879163","data":{"timestamp":" 946788879162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788879738","data":{"timestamp":" 946788879738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788879823","data":{"timestamp":" 946788879823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788880268","data":{"timestamp":" 946788880267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788880831","data":{"timestamp":" 946788880830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788881236","data":{"timestamp":" 946788881236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788882175","data":{"timestamp":" 946788882174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788883055","data":{"timestamp":" 946788883053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TULIPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788883635","data":{"timestamp":" 946788883635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788883892","data":{"timestamp":" 946788883891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788884666","data":{"timestamp":" 946788884664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788887624","data":{"timestamp":" 946788887624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788890027","data":{"timestamp":" 946788890027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788893213","data":{"timestamp":" 946788893212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788895458","data":{"timestamp":" 946788895458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788898014","data":{"timestamp":" 946788898014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788899935","data":{"timestamp":" 946788899934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788901942","data":{"timestamp":" 946788901941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788903995","data":{"timestamp":" 946788903995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788906174","data":{"timestamp":" 946788906173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788912313","data":{"timestamp":" 946788912313"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788913796","data":{"timestamp":" 946788913796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788916011","data":{"timestamp":" 946788916011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788918399","data":{"timestamp":" 946788918398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788919295","data":{"timestamp":" 946788919294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788920421","data":{"timestamp":" 946788920421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788920905","data":{"timestamp":" 946788920905"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788921785","data":{"timestamp":" 946788921785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" KIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788922190","data":{"timestamp":" 946788922189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788922939","data":{"timestamp":" 946788922939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788924263","data":{"timestamp":" 946788924262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788925476","data":{"timestamp":" 946788925476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TUREKEBISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788926027","data":{"timestamp":" 946788926027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788926672","data":{"timestamp":" 946788926671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788929689","data":{"timestamp":" 946788929689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788931962","data":{"timestamp":" 946788931961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788935201","data":{"timestamp":" 946788935201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788936755","data":{"timestamp":" 946788936754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788940063","data":{"timestamp":" 946788940062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788941875","data":{"timestamp":" 946788941875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788945121","data":{"timestamp":" 946788945120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788947471","data":{"timestamp":" 946788947470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788949553","data":{"timestamp":" 946788949553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788951585","data":{"timestamp":" 946788951585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788953253","data":{"timestamp":" 946788953253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788955985","data":{"timestamp":" 946788955984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" JUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788957189","data":{"timestamp":" 946788957188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788958043","data":{"timestamp":" 946788958043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" AMEPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788958646","data":{"timestamp":" 946788958645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788959559","data":{"timestamp":" 946788959559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788959843","data":{"timestamp":" 946788959843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788960497","data":{"timestamp":" 946788960497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788961521","data":{"timestamp":" 946788961521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788962606","data":{"timestamp":" 946788962606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" KUSAFISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788963241","data":{"timestamp":" 946788963241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788963396","data":{"timestamp":" 946788963395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788963800","data":{"timestamp":" 946788963800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788964504","data":{"timestamp":" 946788964504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788967527","data":{"timestamp":" 946788967527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788969749","data":{"timestamp":" 946788969749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788971680","data":{"timestamp":" 946788971680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788973714","data":{"timestamp":" 946788973714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788975878","data":{"timestamp":" 946788975878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788977698","data":{"timestamp":" 946788977698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788980012","data":{"timestamp":" 946788980012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788981892","data":{"timestamp":" 946788981891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788983877","data":{"timestamp":" 946788983877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788985646","data":{"timestamp":" 946788985646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788987465","data":{"timestamp":" 946788987465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788989564","data":{"timestamp":" 946788989564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788991285","data":{"timestamp":" 946788991285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788993763","data":{"timestamp":" 946788993763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788994330","data":{"timestamp":" 946788994330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788994504","data":{"timestamp":" 946788994503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788995288","data":{"timestamp":" 946788995287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" MAKAMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788996109","data":{"timestamp":" 946788996108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788997091","data":{"timestamp":" 946788997091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788998058","data":{"timestamp":" 946788998057"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788999071","data":{"timestamp":" 946788999070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788999829","data":{"timestamp":" 946788999829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" KUUNGANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789000031","data":{"timestamp":" 946789000030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789000648","data":{"timestamp":" 946789000647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789001432","data":{"timestamp":" 946789001432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789005430","data":{"timestamp":" 946789005430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789008831","data":{"timestamp":" 946789008831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789010761","data":{"timestamp":" 946789010761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789013159","data":{"timestamp":" 946789013159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789015835","data":{"timestamp":" 946789015835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789018073","data":{"timestamp":" 946789018073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789019929","data":{"timestamp":" 946789019928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789021952","data":{"timestamp":" 946789021952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789025339","data":{"timestamp":" 946789025339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789027059","data":{"timestamp":" 946789027059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789028875","data":{"timestamp":" 946789028875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789030925","data":{"timestamp":" 946789030925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789033460","data":{"timestamp":" 946789033459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789034304","data":{"timestamp":" 946789034303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789035275","data":{"timestamp":" 946789035273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789035485","data":{"timestamp":" 946789035483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789036137","data":{"timestamp":" 946789036136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789037311","data":{"timestamp":" 946789037311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789038227","data":{"timestamp":" 946789038227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" WATACHIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789038799","data":{"timestamp":" 946789038798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789039065","data":{"timestamp":" 946789039065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789039764","data":{"timestamp":" 946789039763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789042250","data":{"timestamp":" 946789042250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789044371","data":{"timestamp":" 946789044371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789046522","data":{"timestamp":" 946789046522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789049033","data":{"timestamp":" 946789049032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789050976","data":{"timestamp":" 946789050976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789053412","data":{"timestamp":" 946789053411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789055388","data":{"timestamp":" 946789055388"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789057299","data":{"timestamp":" 946789057298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789059466","data":{"timestamp":" 946789059466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789061603","data":{"timestamp":" 946789061603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789064152","data":{"timestamp":" 946789064151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789064214","data":{"timestamp":" 946789064214"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789064312","data":{"timestamp":" 946789064312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 4362d441-06f7-43bb-910a-e0570e1e219e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789078005","data":{"timestamp":" 946789078004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789078596","data":{"timestamp":" 946789078595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789079323","data":{"timestamp":" 946789079322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789079502","data":{"timestamp":" 946789079502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789080276","data":{"timestamp":" 946789080276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789081299","data":{"timestamp":" 946789081299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789087674","data":{"timestamp":" 946789087674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789089364","data":{"timestamp":" 946789089364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789091677","data":{"timestamp":" 946789091677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789093532","data":{"timestamp":" 946789093531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789096332","data":{"timestamp":" 946789096332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789099364","data":{"timestamp":" 946789099364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789101495","data":{"timestamp":" 946789101495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TULIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789102178","data":{"timestamp":" 946789102178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" FOLENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789103430","data":{"timestamp":" 946789103430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789105095","data":{"timestamp":" 946789105095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789105818","data":{"timestamp":" 946789105818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" KUCHOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789106662","data":{"timestamp":" 946789106662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789107526","data":{"timestamp":" 946789107526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789108275","data":{"timestamp":" 946789108275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789108957","data":{"timestamp":" 946789108957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789112182","data":{"timestamp":" 946789112182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789115306","data":{"timestamp":" 946789115305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789117543","data":{"timestamp":" 946789117543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789120249","data":{"timestamp":" 946789120249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789125484","data":{"timestamp":" 946789125484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789129824","data":{"timestamp":" 946789129823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789131654","data":{"timestamp":" 946789131654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789133947","data":{"timestamp":" 946789133946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789136013","data":{"timestamp":" 946789136013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789138839","data":{"timestamp":" 946789138839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TULISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789139383","data":{"timestamp":" 946789139382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789139538","data":{"timestamp":" 946789139538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789139940","data":{"timestamp":" 946789139940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789140775","data":{"timestamp":" 946789140774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789141698","data":{"timestamp":" 946789141698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" KUPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789142395","data":{"timestamp":" 946789142395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789142561","data":{"timestamp":" 946789142561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789143317","data":{"timestamp":" 946789143317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789146019","data":{"timestamp":" 946789146019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789147811","data":{"timestamp":" 946789147811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789149588","data":{"timestamp":" 946789149588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789151523","data":{"timestamp":" 946789151523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789153290","data":{"timestamp":" 946789153290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789155158","data":{"timestamp":" 946789155158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789157457","data":{"timestamp":" 946789157457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789159259","data":{"timestamp":" 946789159259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789161204","data":{"timestamp":" 946789161204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789163714","data":{"timestamp":" 946789163714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TULIFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789164200","data":{"timestamp":" 946789164200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789164729","data":{"timestamp":" 946789164728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789165520","data":{"timestamp":" 946789165520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789166180","data":{"timestamp":" 946789166180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789166846","data":{"timestamp":" 946789166845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789166935","data":{"timestamp":" 946789166935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789167543","data":{"timestamp":" 946789167542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" WIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789170583","data":{"timestamp":" 946789170583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789172388","data":{"timestamp":" 946789172388"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789174251","data":{"timestamp":" 946789174251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789176249","data":{"timestamp":" 946789176249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789178038","data":{"timestamp":" 946789178038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789179800","data":{"timestamp":" 946789179800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789181736","data":{"timestamp":" 946789181736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789183714","data":{"timestamp":" 946789183713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789186263","data":{"timestamp":" 946789186263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789186395","data":{"timestamp":" 946789186395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789187340","data":{"timestamp":" 946789187340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789188423","data":{"timestamp":" 946789188423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789189091","data":{"timestamp":" 946789189091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789189544","data":{"timestamp":" 946789189544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789190182","data":{"timestamp":" 946789190182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789190729","data":{"timestamp":" 946789190728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789191226","data":{"timestamp":" 946789191226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789192611","data":{"timestamp":" 946789192610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789193270","data":{"timestamp":" 946789193269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" KULIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789193876","data":{"timestamp":" 946789193876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789196389","data":{"timestamp":" 946789196389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789198228","data":{"timestamp":" 946789198227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789200251","data":{"timestamp":" 946789200251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789204384","data":{"timestamp":" 946789204384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789206407","data":{"timestamp":" 946789206407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789208674","data":{"timestamp":" 946789208674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789210840","data":{"timestamp":" 946789210840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789212933","data":{"timestamp":" 946789212932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789214627","data":{"timestamp":" 946789214627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789217151","data":{"timestamp":" 946789217151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789219487","data":{"timestamp":" 946789219487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789221679","data":{"timestamp":" 946789221678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789224126","data":{"timestamp":" 946789224126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789224500","data":{"timestamp":" 946789224499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789225502","data":{"timestamp":" 946789225501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789226031","data":{"timestamp":" 946789226030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789226998","data":{"timestamp":" 946789226997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789227641","data":{"timestamp":" 946789227641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789228254","data":{"timestamp":" 946789228254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" YAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789231072","data":{"timestamp":" 946789231071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789233718","data":{"timestamp":" 946789233718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789235657","data":{"timestamp":" 946789235656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789237647","data":{"timestamp":" 946789237647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789239943","data":{"timestamp":" 946789239943"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789241827","data":{"timestamp":" 946789241826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789244412","data":{"timestamp":" 946789244412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789246795","data":{"timestamp":" 946789246795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789247551","data":{"timestamp":" 946789247550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789248375","data":{"timestamp":" 946789248375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" WALIRANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789248881","data":{"timestamp":" 946789248881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" RANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789249832","data":{"timestamp":" 946789249832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789250487","data":{"timestamp":" 946789250486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789251113","data":{"timestamp":" 946789251112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789252050","data":{"timestamp":" 946789252050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789252493","data":{"timestamp":" 946789252493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789252957","data":{"timestamp":" 946789252957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789253922","data":{"timestamp":" 946789253922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" MASHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789256684","data":{"timestamp":" 946789256684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789258934","data":{"timestamp":" 946789258934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789261316","data":{"timestamp":" 946789261315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789263920","data":{"timestamp":" 946789263920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789266548","data":{"timestamp":" 946789266548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789268406","data":{"timestamp":" 946789268405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789270694","data":{"timestamp":" 946789270694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789272905","data":{"timestamp":" 946789272905"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789274981","data":{"timestamp":" 946789274980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789277264","data":{"timestamp":" 946789277264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789279345","data":{"timestamp":" 946789279345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789281718","data":{"timestamp":" 946789281718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789283011","data":{"timestamp":" 946789283011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIPOVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789284744","data":{"timestamp":" 946789284744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789285538","data":{"timestamp":" 946789285538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789286372","data":{"timestamp":" 946789286371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" CHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789286834","data":{"timestamp":" 946789286834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789288047","data":{"timestamp":" 946789288047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" KUZIANGIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789289071","data":{"timestamp":" 946789289071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" MITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789289544","data":{"timestamp":" 946789289544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789290166","data":{"timestamp":" 946789290165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" UANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789293308","data":{"timestamp":" 946789293307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789295839","data":{"timestamp":" 946789295839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789298488","data":{"timestamp":" 946789298488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789302192","data":{"timestamp":" 946789302191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789304062","data":{"timestamp":" 946789304061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789306198","data":{"timestamp":" 946789306198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789308627","data":{"timestamp":" 946789308627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789310390","data":{"timestamp":" 946789310390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789312114","data":{"timestamp":" 946789312114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789313806","data":{"timestamp":" 946789313806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789316520","data":{"timestamp":" 946789316519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789317126","data":{"timestamp":" 946789317126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789318066","data":{"timestamp":" 946789318065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789318263","data":{"timestamp":" 946789318263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789319005","data":{"timestamp":" 946789319005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" VIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789319258","data":{"timestamp":" 946789319258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789319893","data":{"timestamp":" 946789319893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789321277","data":{"timestamp":" 946789321277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789321620","data":{"timestamp":" 946789321620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789322101","data":{"timestamp":" 946789322101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789325827","data":{"timestamp":" 946789325826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789328227","data":{"timestamp":" 946789328227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789330535","data":{"timestamp":" 946789330535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789332373","data":{"timestamp":" 946789332372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789334359","data":{"timestamp":" 946789334359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789336023","data":{"timestamp":" 946789336023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789338328","data":{"timestamp":" 946789338328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789340564","data":{"timestamp":" 946789340564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789342409","data":{"timestamp":" 946789342408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789346404","data":{"timestamp":" 946789346404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789348805","data":{"timestamp":" 946789348805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789349257","data":{"timestamp":" 946789349257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789349910","data":{"timestamp":" 946789349909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789351213","data":{"timestamp":" 946789351213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789351416","data":{"timestamp":" 946789351416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789352030","data":{"timestamp":" 946789352029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789353271","data":{"timestamp":" 946789353271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789353957","data":{"timestamp":" 946789353957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789354801","data":{"timestamp":" 946789354801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" MITUNGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789355224","data":{"timestamp":" 946789355224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789356358","data":{"timestamp":" 946789356358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789357073","data":{"timestamp":" 946789357073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789359773","data":{"timestamp":" 946789359773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789361500","data":{"timestamp":" 946789361500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789362663","data":{"timestamp":" 946789362663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789364644","data":{"timestamp":" 946789364644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789366363","data":{"timestamp":" 946789366363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789368310","data":{"timestamp":" 946789368310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789370460","data":{"timestamp":" 946789370459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789372402","data":{"timestamp":" 946789372402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789374275","data":{"timestamp":" 946789374274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789376008","data":{"timestamp":" 946789376008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789377962","data":{"timestamp":" 946789377962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789380885","data":{"timestamp":" 946789380885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789383463","data":{"timestamp":" 946789383463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789384723","data":{"timestamp":" 946789384722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" ALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789385490","data":{"timestamp":" 946789385489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789386113","data":{"timestamp":" 946789386113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789386887","data":{"timestamp":" 946789386887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789387441","data":{"timestamp":" 946789387441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789388745","data":{"timestamp":" 946789388745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" AKIWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789389259","data":{"timestamp":" 946789389259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789390493","data":{"timestamp":" 946789390493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" KUHUDHURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789391317","data":{"timestamp":" 946789391317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789391532","data":{"timestamp":" 946789391532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789392345","data":{"timestamp":" 946789392345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" KUJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789394923","data":{"timestamp":" 946789394923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789397071","data":{"timestamp":" 946789397070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789399129","data":{"timestamp":" 946789399129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789401039","data":{"timestamp":" 946789401039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789403728","data":{"timestamp":" 946789403728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789406067","data":{"timestamp":" 946789406066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789408786","data":{"timestamp":" 946789408786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789412302","data":{"timestamp":" 946789412302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789414466","data":{"timestamp":" 946789414466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789419651","data":{"timestamp":" 946789419651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789421254","data":{"timestamp":" 946789421254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789423299","data":{"timestamp":" 946789423299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789425555","data":{"timestamp":" 946789425555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789426799","data":{"timestamp":" 946789426799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789427364","data":{"timestamp":" 946789427364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789427447","data":{"timestamp":" 946789427447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789427870","data":{"timestamp":" 946789427870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789428434","data":{"timestamp":" 946789428434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789428845","data":{"timestamp":" 946789428844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789429772","data":{"timestamp":" 946789429772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789430625","data":{"timestamp":" 946789430625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TULIPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789431190","data":{"timestamp":" 946789431190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789431433","data":{"timestamp":" 946789431433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789432187","data":{"timestamp":" 946789432187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789434787","data":{"timestamp":" 946789434787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789437384","data":{"timestamp":" 946789437383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789439184","data":{"timestamp":" 946789439183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789440916","data":{"timestamp":" 946789440916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789442960","data":{"timestamp":" 946789442959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789445351","data":{"timestamp":" 946789445351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789448038","data":{"timestamp":" 946789448038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789450128","data":{"timestamp":" 946789450128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789452132","data":{"timestamp":" 946789452131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789454409","data":{"timestamp":" 946789454409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789456214","data":{"timestamp":" 946789456214"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789458495","data":{"timestamp":" 946789458494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789460906","data":{"timestamp":" 946789460906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789461816","data":{"timestamp":" 946789461815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789462946","data":{"timestamp":" 946789462946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789463432","data":{"timestamp":" 946789463431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789464296","data":{"timestamp":" 946789464295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" KIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789464689","data":{"timestamp":" 946789464689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789465423","data":{"timestamp":" 946789465422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789466728","data":{"timestamp":" 946789466728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789467944","data":{"timestamp":" 946789467943"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TUREKEBISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789468520","data":{"timestamp":" 946789468520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789469168","data":{"timestamp":" 946789469168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789471809","data":{"timestamp":" 946789471809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789474658","data":{"timestamp":" 946789474658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789476597","data":{"timestamp":" 946789476597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789480234","data":{"timestamp":" 946789480234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789481970","data":{"timestamp":" 946789481970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789483697","data":{"timestamp":" 946789483697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789488350","data":{"timestamp":" 946789488350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789490592","data":{"timestamp":" 946789490592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789493976","data":{"timestamp":" 946789493976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789495923","data":{"timestamp":" 946789495923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789497742","data":{"timestamp":" 946789497742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789500478","data":{"timestamp":" 946789500478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" JUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789501681","data":{"timestamp":" 946789501681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789502535","data":{"timestamp":" 946789502535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" AMEPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789503139","data":{"timestamp":" 946789503139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789504052","data":{"timestamp":" 946789504052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789504335","data":{"timestamp":" 946789504335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789504989","data":{"timestamp":" 946789504989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789506012","data":{"timestamp":" 946789506012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789507096","data":{"timestamp":" 946789507096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" KUSAFISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789507730","data":{"timestamp":" 946789507730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789507885","data":{"timestamp":" 946789507885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789508290","data":{"timestamp":" 946789508290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789508995","data":{"timestamp":" 946789508995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789514230","data":{"timestamp":" 946789514230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789516255","data":{"timestamp":" 946789516255"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789518197","data":{"timestamp":" 946789518196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789520669","data":{"timestamp":" 946789520669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789523067","data":{"timestamp":" 946789523067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789525212","data":{"timestamp":" 946789525212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789527636","data":{"timestamp":" 946789527636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789529772","data":{"timestamp":" 946789529772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789532740","data":{"timestamp":" 946789532740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789538803","data":{"timestamp":" 946789538803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789542317","data":{"timestamp":" 946789542317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789544407","data":{"timestamp":" 946789544407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789546127","data":{"timestamp":" 946789546127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789548599","data":{"timestamp":" 946789548598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789549155","data":{"timestamp":" 946789549155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789549328","data":{"timestamp":" 946789549328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789550092","data":{"timestamp":" 946789550092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" MAKAMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789550895","data":{"timestamp":" 946789550895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789551858","data":{"timestamp":" 946789551858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789552812","data":{"timestamp":" 946789552812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789553795","data":{"timestamp":" 946789553795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789554538","data":{"timestamp":" 946789554538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" KUUNGANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789554722","data":{"timestamp":" 946789554722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789555316","data":{"timestamp":" 946789555316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789556100","data":{"timestamp":" 946789556099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789558800","data":{"timestamp":" 946789558800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789561603","data":{"timestamp":" 946789561603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789565923","data":{"timestamp":" 946789565923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789568536","data":{"timestamp":" 946789568536"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789573110","data":{"timestamp":" 946789573110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789575369","data":{"timestamp":" 946789575369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789581126","data":{"timestamp":" 946789581126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789584728","data":{"timestamp":" 946789584728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789587067","data":{"timestamp":" 946789587067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789588983","data":{"timestamp":" 946789588982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789591464","data":{"timestamp":" 946789591464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789593509","data":{"timestamp":" 946789593509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789596043","data":{"timestamp":" 946789596042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789596886","data":{"timestamp":" 946789596886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789597840","data":{"timestamp":" 946789597840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789598033","data":{"timestamp":" 946789598033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789598676","data":{"timestamp":" 946789598676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789599849","data":{"timestamp":" 946789599849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789600742","data":{"timestamp":" 946789600742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" WATACHIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789601306","data":{"timestamp":" 946789601306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789601559","data":{"timestamp":" 946789601559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789602244","data":{"timestamp":" 946789602244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789604855","data":{"timestamp":" 946789604855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789609368","data":{"timestamp":" 946789609368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789611517","data":{"timestamp":" 946789611517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789613323","data":{"timestamp":" 946789613323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789615459","data":{"timestamp":" 946789615459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789617894","data":{"timestamp":" 946789617893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789620766","data":{"timestamp":" 946789620765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789623167","data":{"timestamp":" 946789623167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789624717","data":{"timestamp":" 946789624717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789630519","data":{"timestamp":" 946789630519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789633075","data":{"timestamp":" 946789633075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789633948","data":{"timestamp":" 946789633948"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISEMA"," userResponse":" TULISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789634182","data":{"timestamp":" 946789634182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789634836","data":{"timestamp":" 946789634836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789635320","data":{"timestamp":" 946789635320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789636684","data":{"timestamp":" 946789636684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789637816","data":{"timestamp":" 946789637816"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUBADILISHE"," userResponse":" TUBADILISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789638549","data":{"timestamp":" 946789638548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789639256","data":{"timestamp":" 946789639256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789642240","data":{"timestamp":" 946789642240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789644246","data":{"timestamp":" 946789644246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789646607","data":{"timestamp":" 946789646606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789648833","data":{"timestamp":" 946789648833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789652989","data":{"timestamp":" 946789652989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789655415","data":{"timestamp":" 946789655415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789657656","data":{"timestamp":" 946789657655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUBADILISHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789659663","data":{"timestamp":" 946789659663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789661490","data":{"timestamp":" 946789661490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789663119","data":{"timestamp":" 946789663119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789663583","data":{"timestamp":" 946789663583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789664217","data":{"timestamp":" 946789664216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789665280","data":{"timestamp":" 946789665280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789665757","data":{"timestamp":" 946789665757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789666732","data":{"timestamp":" 946789666731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789668116","data":{"timestamp":" 946789668115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATATUA"," userResponse":" TUKATATUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789668599","data":{"timestamp":" 946789668599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" SHIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789668952","data":{"timestamp":" 946789668952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789676307","data":{"timestamp":" 946789676307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789677856","data":{"timestamp":" 946789677856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789679730","data":{"timestamp":" 946789679730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789682148","data":{"timestamp":" 946789682147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789685632","data":{"timestamp":" 946789685632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789688465","data":{"timestamp":" 946789688465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789694343","data":{"timestamp":" 946789694343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATATUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789699620","data":{"timestamp":" 946789699619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789703461","data":{"timestamp":" 946789703461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789705475","data":{"timestamp":" 946789705475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789705634","data":{"timestamp":" 946789705634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 2d176b50-64c2-4b29-8617-d9e55622c052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789717162","data":{"timestamp":" 946789717162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789717386","data":{"timestamp":" 946789717385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789718348","data":{"timestamp":" 946789718348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789719621","data":{"timestamp":" 946789719621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789722490","data":{"timestamp":" 946789722490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789723334","data":{"timestamp":" 946789723334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789723648","data":{"timestamp":" 946789723648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789724880","data":{"timestamp":" 946789724880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789728359","data":{"timestamp":" 946789728358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789729342","data":{"timestamp":" 946789729342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789729595","data":{"timestamp":" 946789729595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789730538","data":{"timestamp":" 946789730538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789733408","data":{"timestamp":" 946789733408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789734441","data":{"timestamp":" 946789734441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789734914","data":{"timestamp":" 946789734914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789739428","data":{"timestamp":" 946789739427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946789739501","data":{"timestamp":" 946789739501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791621863","data":{"timestamp":" 946791621862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_074331"," gameId":" 0ed1d546-048e-47af-afc8-418c6ac08c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}